corrections = {
    "UT Austin Invitational 18-19, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "25",
        "explanation": "Takes abt 1 hour to climb ->  ~500 kcal burned, 1 mol ATP = 7.3 kcal\n500/7.3 * 6E23 = 4e25 molecules",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #5": {
        "question": "What is 2^12?",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "log(2) * 12 = .30103 * 12 ~= 3.6 ==> 4",
        "credit": "choi"
    },
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #25": {
        "question": "What is the probability of a randomly selected person on Earth having an IQ of above 200?",
        "answer": "-11",
        "explanation": "normCdf with mean as 100 and SD as 15 gives 1.32e-11",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 17-18, #19": {
        "question": "[Question #6: Yo mamma so fat, she took all the Big Macs sold in the US last year and gobbled \u2019em right up! How many pounds of fat are in yo mamma now? Assume that yo mama ain\u2019t burning any o\u2019 those calories, cuz ain\u2019t nobody got time for that!]\n\nYo mamma not only fat, she so fat that she is seriously concerned about her health and well-being. How many hours would she have to run in order to burn off all those delicious Big Macs from question 6?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #25": {
        "question": "How many seconds would it take the average nuclear plant to generate the amount of energy found in the question above? (Question above: How much energy has been used through the consumption of gasoline by all the cars in the world since the invention of the automobile?)",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #6": {
        "question": "What is 10 ^ (3log(5) + log(20) + 2log(2)) ? Here log denotes the base 10 logarithm.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #15": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "Average person drinks about 2 liters of water a day. 2 liters/day * 365 days/year * 80 years = 58400 liters.",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #43": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "Pew Research Center says it is 22 million people in 2023. Census.gov says that it was 27.6\nmillion people in 2021. It will likely not be 50+ million in 2023",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #13": {
        "question": "How many calories do I burn if I climb the Great Wall one stair at a time?",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "3100 stairs on the Great Wall of China. 1 stair burns 0.17 calories. 3100 *.17 = 527 calories",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #6": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "63 games with 2 possible winners each. 63 * log(2) = 18.96",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #18 [2018 Brown Q19]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "Height of Washington Monument is 169.29 m. Thickness of a quarter is 1.75 mm and its mass is 6 g. 169.29 m * 1 quarter / .00175 m * 6 grams / 1 quarter * 1 metric ton / E6 grams = .58 metric tons or about 1 metric ton.",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #75 [2019 Polytechnic Q19]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "According to avma.org in 2018, there were 76,811,305 dogs as pets.",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #1": {
        "question": "What is 2^2017?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #11 [2019 Eastside / Haslett Q14]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "Lots of sources saying 30-40 trillion or around 37 trillion",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "What is (1/7)^35?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2019 LISO Q14]": {
        "question": "Your airplane masses 8 grams. How many fully loaded Airbus A380s is that?",
        "answer": "-8",
        "explanation": "fully loaded airbus is ~1e6 lbs or ~5e8 lbs, answer is 8/(5e8) or approx -8",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #15": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "https://en.m.wikipedia.org/wiki/Molar_ionization_energies_of_the_elements\n\nnot specified which ionization energy but definitely not 9995",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #66 [2019 Northmont Q5]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-29",
        "explanation": "Mass of adult housefly - 0.0450g / mass of Jupiter 1.90E+27 = 2.368E-29",
        "credit": "5omil"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "earth to moon: 3.8e8 meters\npenny thickness: 1.52e-3 meters\nanswer: 2.5e11 pennies",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #7": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-1",
        "explanation": "Speed of a bullet is 180-1500 m/s. It does not take 10^11 seconds for a bullet to travel 100 meters.",
        "credit": "Hudson Tien (hsin_tn)"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 22-23, #33": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "sun to earth = 1.5e11 m\nSR 71 blackbird top speed = 9.8e2 m/s\n= e8 seconds",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "US debt is 32.7 trillion, US GDP is around 25 trillion. 32.7 - 25 trillion = 7.7 trillion",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #34": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1930",
        "explanation": "2023 * log(9) = 1930",
        "credit": "IOnlyShoot3s"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #16": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-10",
        "explanation": "3934km = e-10 parsecs",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #26": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "14",
        "explanation": "US school day is on average 6-7 hours with ~180 school days per year, so about 4.2 million seconds are spent in school per student. Multiply this by the 49.4 million students in the US to obtain a number of 2.1*10^14 seconds.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 18-19, #13": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "10^15 m/s is superluminal, answer should be 8 since c is 3x10^8 m/s, neutron would have to be moving very close to that",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-4",
        "explanation": "A fermi test is 50 minutes; 50 min/test * hr/60 min * day/24 hrs * year / 365 days = .0001 years/test or 10E-4",
        "credit": "Elytraflight, Milpitas Scioly"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "There are 365 episodes of Teletubbies according to Google, hence 1 episode per day should last 1 year (10^0)",
        "credit": "Elytraflight, MHS Scioly"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #16": {
        "question": "Such a computer: (An Intel i7 chip if all CMOS transistors were replaced with BJTs on an infinite breadboard, assuming that all holes on the breadboard are filled and used solely for the BJT pins.)",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11": {
        "question": "Include the answer to the question above?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Refers to another question that we don't know about",
        "credit": "fryed_eggs"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #18": {
        "question": "How many dislikes does this same video (the most viewed video) have?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #16 [2018 Harvard Q4]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "Google how many red blood cells are in the human body? and the answer is 2.4 million cells per second times by 60 to change it to minute and you get 144 million cells per minute.",
        "credit": "Staplers"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "debt=$3*10^13, citizens=3*10^8 people ($3*10^13)/(3*10^8people)=$10^5/person -> 5",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #37": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-8",
        "explanation": "Red light wavelength is about 650nm (6.5E-7 m). Length of a football field (including endzones) is about 110m. 6.5E-7 / 110 = 5.9E-9. Thus, Fermi answer is (-8)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #45": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-6",
        "explanation": "Red light wavelength is about 650 nm = 6.5E-7m = Fermi answer (-6)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #39": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "35 trillion red blood cells in human body, see source: https://www.texasheart.org/heart-health/heart-information-center/topics/blood-cells/#:~:text=Red%20blood%20cells%20carry%20oxygen,span%20of%20about%20120%20days.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 22-23, #17": {
        "question": "Total hours of television watched in the US every day.",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "The average person in the us could watch 1.5 hours (500,000,000/331,900,000) to 15 hours (4,999,999,999/331,900,000) and it would fall under 10^9 (1,000,000,000) hours total.",
        "credit": "sharp59#6969"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "They say that it took Thomas Edison 1,000 tries to successfully create the first lightbulb. How many Navajo Indians died in that amount of time?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #10": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "6.3% is above 5, which means the Fermi answer should be 1",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #12": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "The height of mount Everest is 8849.9 meters which when converted to nanometers is 10^13.",
        "credit": "BossCrusher667"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #98 [2019 ATX Regionals Q41]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "The area of the USA is around 10 million km^2 which is 10^7",
        "credit": "BossCrusher667"
    },
    "University of Michigan Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "avocados grow at 2.5 ft/year, takes 100 years to grow 300 ft. so 10^4 days",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #32": {
        "question": "Suppose you play a game with the following rules: you roll a fair 20 sided die five times and flip a fair coin. If you roll a twenty every time and get heads, then you win $1,000,000,000. You must pay $20 to play the game. How much money do you expect to win from playing the game 1,000,000 times?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2019 WWPN Q3]": {
        "question": "If I had a nickel for every time an American driver was pulled over for speeding, how many years would it take for me to become the richest person in the world?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "The richest person has 280 billion net worth. That means you need 56 billion nickels and the average is 41 million people an year. I think this question might be old",
        "credit": "lordofthesnowleopards (discord)"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #32": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "in nanometers, 380 nanometers becomes 2 for fermi",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "When you put 2^32 in a calculator, you get 4294967296 which is 4.2*10^9 so the answer is 9",
        "credit": "BTHS Science Olympiad"
    },
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #25": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "The ISS has an orbital velocity of ~7000 m/s",
        "credit": "trainboi01"
    },
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #15": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "37",
        "explanation": "did the original correcter misread the unit for a barn????",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (randomsci) 22-23, #23": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "24",
        "explanation": "It's asking for the moles of the water in the mol of moles, a mol of moles has 6.02x10^23 moles in it, so thats how many moles of water are in it. For the answer to be 48 it would have to be asking for the molecules of water.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #3": {
        "question": "0.1^89",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "1^89 is 1... which happens to be a fermi answer of 0.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #40": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "molar mass of benzene is 78.11g which is 7.8e7 micrograms, making the answer 8 not 7 since you round up.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #67 [2018 WWPN Tryouts Q1]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "25",
        "explanation": "24 in each mol, i doubt you have over 100 mols in a cup of water cause that would be a kilogram",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 17-18, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "23",
        "explanation": "There are 1.335x10^21 liters of water in the oceans, and since there are about 200 teaspoons in a liter, the answer should be 2x10^23->23.",
        "credit": "emptiespace on disc"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #85 [2018 U Georgia Q2]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "Google is right, but here's a full solution: Each base pair stores 2 bits of information (as it is one of 4 possible choices), and there are 30 billion base pairs in the human genome, so 3*10^8*2/(8*10^6) megabytes which is 3.",
        "credit": "bibob or emptiespace"
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #16": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "26",
        "explanation": "Idk what the answer is exactly, so I'm reverting to original answer. However, previous correction's logic is incomplete. There are 26^26 ways of choosing the letters, but some are equivalent. if your sequence contains 3 copies of the same letter, then this method would count that sequence 3^2=9 times. These copies must be removed, thus making a drastically smaller answer",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #131 [2019 New Trier Q10]": {
        "question": "How many licks to the center of a tootsie pop?",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "Google and nigahiga",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #5": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-1",
        "explanation": "The answer is requested in kg. The weight is 174g and is about 10^-1 in kg.",
        "credit": "uknow4546"
    },
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "15",
        "explanation": "6.7*10^14 is the exact answer and would be 15 in Fermi.",
        "credit": "uknow4546"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #36": {
        "question": "What percentage is that volume compared to mL of water on Earth? [That volume: mL of blood does our heart pumps each day]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #60": {
        "question": "The Ackermann function is defined by \n\u2022 A(0, n) = n + 1 \u2022 A(m, 0) = A(m \u2212 1, 1)\n\u2022 A(m, n) = A(m \u2212 1; A(m, n \u2212 1)) \nSome values include: A(2, 3) = 9 and A(4, 1) = 65533\nWhat is A(4, 2)? [SI/2017 USD]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25": {
        "question": "The current meerkat population is about 500,000 Approximately how many of these meerkats will be murdered by their own species if we follow all of them to their cause of death? Hint: Meerkats have been deemed the \"most murderous\" mammal species.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "BTHS SciOly"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #27": {
        "question": "43^29",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "It looks like they meant 43^29 since the answer would be 47",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #6": {
        "question": "How tall is Mount Everest (in meters)?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "A study in the journal Earth Surface Processes and Landforms, written by Dr. Robert A. Morton of the U.S. Geological Survey, predicted that there are 7.5*10^18 grains of sand on earth. Based off other sources this is also the accepted number in academia.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #33 [2018 Westlake Q47]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-19",
        "explanation": "7e-20 is definitely FA -19, not -21",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #33": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "238,900 miles to the moon * 1 hour / 3 miles (average walking pace) * 60 mins / 1 hr * 60 sec / 1 min = 286,680,000 seconds, or 2.8 * 10^8, answer is 8",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #10": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-6",
        "explanation": "Rice tuition is about $28,605 for one semester, so the fraction that a nickel takes up is 0.05/28605 = 1.7e-6, so the answer is -6.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "Maybe people got less interested in making soup or something, but 300 million->8 results show up if you look it up on a standard school laptop.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #7": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "21",
        "explanation": "Gm...\nSurface area of Moon is 3.8 10^13 m^2...\nso Volume of Glass.. is.. 1.9 * 10^12 m^3 OR 1.9 * 10^18 cm^3\nTHUS... around 4 * 10^18 gram or 4 * 10^21 milligram\n\nRB",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #110 [2019 Monta Vista Q22]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "The US GDP is 2*10^13 USD and the average cost of a car is 3.5*10^4 USD.  When you divide these 2 you get 6.5*10^8 and then you round up to get 10^9",
        "credit": "BTHS SciOly"
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #15": {
        "question": "How many galaxies are in our local group.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "This question is currently asking how many galaxies are in one galaxy, which is just 1, or 0 in fermi notation.",
        "credit": "X"
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #12": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "Google says that the Atlantic is 4.9 million meters, and that a snail speed is 0.01 meters per second. This gives 4900000/0.01->8 as the fermi answer.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (randomsci) 22-23, #27": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "78",
        "explanation": "The Google Calculator says 6x10^77 -> 78 for the fermi answer.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #38": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Google says that it takes 820 hours to walk to the end of a minecraft world. Multiply this by 60 to get 49200. This gets pretty close to the 5 midpoint, but does round down to 4.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #49": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "Paper thickness is 0.5 mm = 5e-4 m, blue light wavelength is about 400 nm = 4e-7 m, dividing gives 1.25e3, so the answer is 3.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #22": {
        "question": "Evaluate (\u03c0e)^(\u03c0e)",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #19": {
        "question": "It's Chris's birthday! How many times should he roll a fair 10^10000-sided die before expecting to see a number twice (not necessarily consecutively) ?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #11": {
        "question": "What is the sum of the numbers from 1 to 10^5 ?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Sum of numbers 1-105 is 5,565, or 4.",
        "credit": "Asher N"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #7": {
        "question": "On a chess board, suppose that the queens must be arranged in a manner such that none of the queens could capture another (i.e. none of the queens can be under attack). How many such configurations are possible? Do not include boards that are reflections, rotations, etc.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "This helps to clarify what the question is about. It was kind of \"cut off\" in the beginning.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #41": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "This is an interest question, to solve this you do 1500*(1.05)^85 which results in approximately 950,00, if continuously compounded it would be about 105,000, both of which are rounded to 100,000 which in fermi notation is 5",
        "credit": "iampotatoz"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #6 [2019 Virginia Tech Q4]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "22",
        "explanation": "Volume of Pacific Ocean is 5E+17m^3, roughly 1e+4 sheets of paper fit in a cubic meter. Should be 21 or 22.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #22 [2018 Acton-Box Q15]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "Searched it up on google. It is around 20 million (10^7)",
        "credit": "Purple"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #46": {
        "question": "What is the half-life of Carbon-14 in seconds? [Use SI Units / 2017 USD]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "The mass of the sun and the solar mass is around the same, where did 6 come from",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #80 [2019 U Chicago Q21]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "I have been listening to Gucci Gang since 1776 and I can confirm this answer is right",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #109 [2018 U Florida Regionals Q14]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "I used a pipette and confirmed it myself",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #96 [2018 Monta Vista Tryouts Q1]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "27",
        "explanation": "The volume of is 10^21 meters and the weigh of water per cubic meter is 10^3 kg and kg to g is 10^3. Mutiply everything and we get 10^27",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "How tall is Mount Everest in meters?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "how hard is it to add 2",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #20": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "18",
        "explanation": "https://www.usgs.gov/faqs/how-much-natural-water-there#:~:text=Earth%20is%20estimated%20to%20hold,glaciers%20(fresh)%2024%2C064%2C000%20cubic%20kilometers",
        "credit": "Discord: errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #17 [2018 Westlake Q24]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "https://www.aar.org/wp-content/uploads/2021/02/AAR-Ohio-State-Fact-Sheet.pdf \n\nThe Association of American Railroads states in the above pdf that there's 5,139 miles of railroad tracks, so the answer would round up to 4. I hope I'm not coming off sounding mean; just want the info as accurate as possible  \ud83d\udc4d",
        "credit": "thatperson2647"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #30": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "16 Disney-owned movies were released in 2016; an average of 2 hours per movie moves around 97,000 seconds. Final answer is 5",
        "credit": "@tripleqgaming (discord)"
    },
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #27": {
        "question": "A particle is placed in a rigid box (the walls are impenetrable). What is the probability of finding it anywhere within (percent)? For reference, the one dimensional wave equation is \u03c8=Asin[(n\u03c0/L)*x]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Clarifying the problem because it's 2 as in 100%",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #41": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Most sources (Statista, for instance) suggest that the average Japanese eats just under 100 pounds of rice per year. This is around a bowl of rice a day, if we were to make a reasonable guess during a test. The Japanese life expectancy also happens to be just under 100 (mid-80s). 10^2 * 10^2 produces a Fermi number of 4.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #133 [2019 Dartmouth Q16]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "100 pizzas * $10/pizza * 100 pennies/dollar = 10^5\n\nCJB",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #73 [2019 Northmont Q75]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "12 bacteria on 4 sq cm of skin",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (rafaelnadal) 17-18, #34": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "real answer would be n where 300*2^n=c",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "The average square foot of grass has 3,000 blades (https://www.quora.com/Has-anyone-ever-calculated-how-many-blades-of-grass-are-in-a-typical-lawn#:~:text=The%20average%20square%20foot%20of,Oklahoma%20Museum%20of%20Natural%20History%20.), so one foot likely contacts about a tenth of that area (average foot is 100 cm^2 = 0.1 ft^2), so about 300 blades are contacted",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #111 [2019 SOUP Q38]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "According to the Cleveland Clinic, humans breath around 12-18 times per minute. The average test taker could, using simple observation, presume a similar rate. There are around 5 * 10^5 minutes in a year. That's a range of 6-9 * 10^6, which provides a Fermi answer of 7. Even without this knowledge, an answer of 9 suggests around 30 breaths per second, with is plainly wrong up or down an order of magnitude.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #2": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "The enrollment in 2017-2018 was 5,260, meaning that the fermi number should be 4",
        "credit": "King Von"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #18": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "log of [44^9 (characters expected for the monkeys to type out one \"GOOD SOUP\") divided by 400 characters per minute (100 wpm = 400 cpm)]",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2018 Princeton Q A39]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-5",
        "explanation": "Volume of a grain of rice is about 0.02 mL = 2e-5 L, so the fraction of the 2L bottle occupied is 1e-5",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #21": {
        "question": "How many primes are less than 10^100?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "greg"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 21-22, #36": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "27",
        "explanation": "Solar constant (flux) is about 1368 W/m^2 (note W = J/s), so energy captured in a minute is 60s * 1368 W/m^2 = 82000 J. Energy consumption of a 1600 lumen lightbulb is about 15 W, so the lightbulb stays on for 82000 J / 15 W = 5500 s. A jiffy is 3e-24 seconds, so converting to jiffies, the time is 1.8e27 jiffies, so the answer is 27.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "Your heart beats once per second at least, 1.5 e7 seconds in half of a year (six months)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #2": {
        "question": "How many NERDS ropes would it take to wrap around Mars?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "what does it mean \"in miles\" sir?????",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #12": {
        "question": "Find 3^33",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #18": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-11",
        "explanation": "K.E. = 1/2 m v^2 = 1/2 * 1.67 * 10^-27 * (1.5 * 10^8)^2 =",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #36": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "3*10^8 m/s * 60 s/minute * 36 inch/meter (also google)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "idk the intended question but hour per hour is really sussy",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rickards SO Invitational 22-23, #42": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5190",
        "explanation": "Nah 5190 is right, its log1(54^3000)\u2014log(10^6), which is a fermi answer",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #17": {
        "question": "How many feathers equal the weight of the heaviest slug species?",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Heaviest slug species (California slug) is 0.25 pounds, weight of a feather is 8.2 milligrams. 13,829 feathers equal the weight of a California slug)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Harvard Invitational 22-23, #4": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "38",
        "explanation": "2 mols released per tree per year, 12 trees, 2 + 12 + 24 = 38",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #53 [2018 Westlake Q27]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "1 General Sherman tree is 84 meters. Distance to the moon is 3.8e8m. Dividing gives 4.5e6 -> 6",
        "credit": "TheBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #38": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "16",
        "explanation": "whether using simple or compound interest, 1000(1.03)^1000 or 1000e^(1000*.03) gives 16",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "Volume of m&m is about 0.6 mL, available volume of car is about 2000 L (3000L before subtracting stuff like engine, seats, etc.), 2000L / (6e-4 L) = 3.33 million, so the answer is 6",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #41": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "the size n is not shown (unless this is intentional)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #2": {
        "question": "What is 7^45?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "caret not shown, the answer 38 thus makes no sense (745 -> 3)",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #5": {
        "question": "The largest prime number discovered to date is 2^74,207,281 - 1. How many digits does this number have?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "missing caret and +1",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #3 [2018 Princeton Q B9]": {
        "question": "What is the number of cells in an adult male human body?",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "According to a new analysis of more than 1,500 papers, the average adult male human has around 36 trillion cells \u2014 that's 36 followed by 12 zeros \u2014 while adult females have 28 trillion and 10-year-old children have about 17 trillion.",
        "credit": "Troy Athens SciOly"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #13": {
        "question": "What fraction of the distance from the Earth to the Moon is this height? [Height of all the light bulbs sold in a year stacked together]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #42": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "16",
        "explanation": "google it lol",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #43": {
        "question": "How many iron atoms are on the tip of a safety pin (the pointy part)?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "typically the head of a pin refers to the round part",
        "credit": "P JAYA"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #125 [2018 Centerville Q18]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "I dont know if the fizz is right here, but if the answer is 5g=50->2, g is less than 10, so the answer should be 1.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #39": {
        "question": "How many ways are there to make change for $10?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #34 [2019 Captains Exchange: NCSSM Q15]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "Average of 20 kids per class * 30 pages per student = 600 pages which rounds to 3",
        "credit": "AC"
    },
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #3": {
        "question": "Assume that in a game of Rock-Paper-Scissors, the hands played by both participants are chosen completely randomly with an equal chance of choosing Rock, Paper, or Scissors. If the two choose the same hand, they do another round. What is the probability the two play the same hand exactly 72 times before finally declaring a winner?",
        "answer": "-35",
        "explanation": "The probability of a tie is 1 (the first player can choose anything) * 1/3 (probability of the second player choosing the same one (1 out of 3)). 1 * 1/3 = 1/3, and the probability of that happening 72 times in a row is (1/3)^72, which is approximately 10^-35.",
        "credit": "JazzyX"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #35 [2019 Solon Q9]": {
        "question": "What is the distance from Pluto to the sun in kilometers?",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "average distance is 5.9billion km according to NASA",
        "credit": "john"
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #47": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "dump truck volume is 10 m^3 and grand canyon is like 4 * 10^12 m^2",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "Ohio State Invitational 22-23, #8": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "A drop of water has a volume of 0.05 mL, and we are adding one drop every second, so the total volume in an hour is 3600 s/hr * 0.05 mL/s = 180 mL = 0.18 L/hr. Olympic swimming pool has a volume of 2.5e6 L, so the time in hours it takes to fill up the swimming pool is (2.5e6 L) / (0.18 L/hr) = 1.39e7 hours, so the answer is 7 (basically, the original answer is correct: someone corrected the answer to 11, which is wrong because they had units of seconds instead of hours)",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #37": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "each grain of sand is -13 m^3, empire state building is 6m^3, so 19 grains are required",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #82 [2019 Captains Exchange: Irvine Q10]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "i mean it never specified front/back, 91 pages is 2",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #19": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "According to a new report, the average cost per inmate in New York's prisons is $167,731 per year.  - first google search",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #26 [2018 Aviation Q5]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "27",
        "explanation": "Volume of earth is 1e21m^3 = 1e27 mL, each skittle is about 0.5-1 mL, resulting in an answer of 1-2e27 skittles in the earth.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #105 [2019 Polytechnic Q24]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-6",
        "explanation": "bro is lying through his teeth",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #60 [2019 Boca Raton Tryouts Q11]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "bro its not a hard problem lol",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #2": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "the original question did not ask how far it could write but how many pencils would it take so the assumption would be to take the length of the pencil which would be 18 cm and it would take approximetly 2 x 10^8 pencils to circle the earth",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #25": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "21",
        "explanation": "Volume of the Pacific Ocean is 7x10^20 liters. A soup can is 12 fluid ounces->0.35 liters. 7/0.35=20->2x10^21->21 cans needed to fill the Pacific Ocean",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #47": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "Fastest plan goes 11850 km/h. Circumference of Earth is ~40,075 km. 40,075/11850 is ~3.38",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "\"answer was Not sure, but it sure isn't 10\" was the original corrected answer :/ The sun has a radius of 6.96*10^8 meters, so it's surface area is 6.1*10^18 m^2. Newspaper sizes vary quite a bit with different sources getting different numbers. The lower bound seems to be 279 mm x 533 mm and the upper seems to be 597 mm x 749 mm, but luckily for us this means that about 2-6 newspapers fit in a square meter (using lower and upper bounds for paper size) so the answer regardless of dimensions is 19 (range of 1.2-3.6e19).",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #36 [2019 Boca Raton Tryouts Q29]": {
        "question": "How much does Bill Gates\u2019 net worth weigh in 10 dollar bills? Express your answer in grams.",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "Gate's net worth is at a magnitude of 11, ten dollar bills make it ^10 bills, 1 bill is 1 gram.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #3": {
        "question": "What fraction (expressed as a decimal) of positive integers less than 10^100 are perfect squares?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "BTHS SciOly"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #5": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "8 people in germany, 2 liters per person",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #20": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "The Philippines is an archipelago that comprises 7,641 islands --> rounds up to 4.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #14": {
        "question": "How big is Duke\u2019s campus (including every part of Duke-owned land) according to Google in cm^2?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "How many meters tall would stacking all of these light bulbs be? [All the light bulbs sold in a year]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #12": {
        "question": "How many of the world's tallest building stacked on top of each other would reach this height? [Height of all the light bulbs sold in a year stacked together]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #17": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "\"With good reason, the Swiss are the world\u2019s most enthusiastic rail users, traveling an average of 2,450 kilometers every year by train.\"\n\nhttps://www.cnn.com/travel/article/world-record-train-switzerland/index.html\n\nLikely the original answer was in regards to km, but the real answer should be in meters, like the question asks for...",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #39": {
        "question": "What is the volume of air breathed by the whole US population each month in liters?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Missing units...",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #116 [2019 Columbia Q3]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "37",
        "explanation": "4.2 million solar masses * 2e30 kg/solar mass = 8.4e36 kg, so the answer is 37",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #8": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "30 days * 24 hrs/day * 30 mm/hr = 21600",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-10",
        "explanation": "that answers in meters assuming its 1 sheet",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #38": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "68",
        "explanation": "bro whoever made this test is incompetent",
        "credit": "Craig B"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2018 Westlake Q44]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "There are 6e18 electrons in a coulomb. Given that wattage is equal to amperage times voltage, at a standard US voltage of 120, that means there's half an amp running through a 60 watt bulb. 6e18 electrons divided by 0.5 amps is a 1.2e19. Likewise, if we use a more global voltage of 240 volts, that would mean a quarter of an amp is running through a 60 watt bulb. 6e18 electrons divided by 0.25 amps is 2.4e19, which would also be 19. Not sure why the original answer was negative.",
        "credit": "cubicfrog (disc)"
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #3": {
        "question": "How many dead skin cells are shed by all the people on Earth each year?",
        "answer": "20",
        "explanation": "40,000 per minute, 525,000 minutes in a year, 8 bil people in the world --> 1.68*e20",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #1 [2018 Westlake Q64]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-23",
        "explanation": "Mass of earth is 6*10^24 kg, average mass of man is 80 kg -> 80/(6*10^24) = 1.3*10^-23, answer is -23",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #19": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "10^6 liters in an olympic swimming pool, ~5 balls in a liter, 10^7 balls total",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 23-24, #9": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "5 is a fibonacci number for which F_n/F_n-1 is within 5% of phi. The percent error for 5/3 compared to phi is surprisingly low at only ~3%, so the answer to the question is 1.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #114 [2019 Solon Q10]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "google the thickness ur tweaking",
        "credit": "Ryan park"
    },
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #53": {
        "question": "The n-th Fermat number is defined as F_n = 2^(2^n) + 1. What is log(F_2023)? Here log denotes the base-10 logarithm.",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "bibob/pikapika007"
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #49": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "10 electrons per molecule of water (2*1 + 8), each mole of water has N_A = 6.022*10^23 molecules of water, final answer is 6*10^24 which is 25",
        "credit": "bibob/pikapika007"
    },
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #26": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "20*12*2= 480 m^3, 480*1000*1000 = 4.8e8 ml, 1 drop of water is 0.05 mL, 4.8e8/0.05 = 9.6e9 which rounds to 10.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "The number of digits is 10^1.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2019 Duke Q5]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "According to the University of St. Andrews, the Sun's core has a density of around 160 g/cm^3.",
        "credit": "Trippy"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #4": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "150",
        "explanation": "150.5 is 3 x 10^150 so it does not round up",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rickards Invitational 23-24, #45": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "not sure what the answer is but if theres only 19 grains of sand on earth there cant be 24 in the sahara",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #44": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "14",
        "explanation": "earth is e15 sq m, about -1 air pods/sq m",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-2",
        "explanation": "Dude the explanation is literally wrong idk what this guy is thinking. 1 cubic meter is 10^6 cm^3, not 10^4\n\nHoly shit please actually check your answer before you submit corrections we get it you got it wrong deal with it",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "distance from earth to sun is at least 10^11 meters, cannot be less than 11",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Palo Alto Tryouts 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "How many different books have been published in the world?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "The fermi answer 8 is given as the number of published books in the world, not the total copies of books in the world.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Text is probably a typo and the Q should be revised, but 41,124 is 4.1124*10^4 or 4.",
        "credit": "Trippy (@tripleqgaming on Discord)"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 22-23, #12": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-5",
        "explanation": "if its a ratio of revolutionary to ww1 thats R/W which should be negative",
        "credit": "Him"
    },
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #40": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-18",
        "explanation": "It says (1/3)^100 but it should be (2/3)^100",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #77 [2019 Cornell Q28]": {
        "question": "How many liters of gasoline does the average american use in their lifetime",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "nom nom gasoline",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UMass Amherst Invitational 22-23, #34": {
        "question": "Jalal flips an unfair coin (heads 3 10 of the time and tails 7 10 of the time) 50 times and calls it an experiment. On average, how many experiments will Jalal have to conduct until he flips at least 48 tails in one experiment?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #11": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "Speed of S waves is 1-8 km/s (for our purposes we will take the average and go 4 km/s), san francisco to syracuse is 4000 km (3926 km but close enough), 4000/4 = 1000 seconds = 1*10^6 ms which is 6",
        "credit": "bibob/pikapika007"
    },
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #12": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "google says 3 x 10^19",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #2": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "48",
        "explanation": "moon volume is 2e25 mL, which is 1.2e24 moles of water, which is 7.4e47 molecules, which is 1.5e48 hydrogen atoms",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #25": {
        "question": "What is the volume of a golf ball measured in cubic hectometers?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #30": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "602051",
        "explanation": "WolframAlpha gives CatalanNumber[1000000] = 5.5*10^602051.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #2": {
        "question": "How many carbon atoms fit from the distance from sea level to the highest point on earth?",
        "answer": "14",
        "explanation": "everest 8800m = e4 m \ncarbon atom 1 angstrom = e-10m \n\n14 m ?",
        "credit": "evanescent"
    },
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #34": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "1 atm ~= 760mmHg which is 3",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #96 [2018 Monta Vista Tryouts Q15]": {
        "question": "How many small calories does the sun output per second?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "the sun outputs 26 watts so for the answer to be 26 it would need to be small calories which can be ambiguous",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #17": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "4e12 / 4e-7 = e19",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #35 [2018 SOUP Q25]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "The earth's circumference (\"arc length\") is 4e7 m, there are 1e12 picometers in a meter, so the arc length is 4e19 pm, leaving an answer of 19",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #21": {
        "question": "If everyone in the world were to stand side-by-side (shoulder to shoulder with no gaps) to form a circle, what would be the diameter of the circle, in human hair widths?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "ambiguous whether it's human hair lengths or widths",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #8": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "22",
        "explanation": "Breath = 0.5L, density of air = 1g/L, air is mostly N2 with molar mass of about 30g/mole, 0.5L*1g/L=0.5g, 0.5g*(6*10^23 molecules)/30g=10^22->22",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #50": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "whoever did the original correction might be sped",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #15 [2018 Mesa-Wilson Q43]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "In practical terms of electric power, one potato can produce approximately . 5 volts of energy. However, did you know that by boiling the potato, you can get it to produce 5 volts instead? For reference, this is about half of the energy of an average AA battery - google",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #9": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-7",
        "explanation": "20 m / (3 x 10^8 m/s) = 6.67 x 10^-8 s",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #47": {
        "question": "What is 42!? [Use SI Units / 2017 USD]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Question text originally contained formatting error which showed the answer.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 17-18, #34": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "the explanation is wrong cause like, it was there for 13 years assuming that they were talking about the september in 2017 before this test was given. i mean mit is probably right man. 13*30m is like 400m so 8",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #44 [2018 SOUP Q4]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "23",
        "explanation": "internet says that for the atmosphere, there are 10^23 molecules of gas. a room is likely about 15 m^3, but since the air is 1/5 oxygen, then the number of oxygen molecules should be 3 * 10^23",
        "credit": "me"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "86400/47 = 1838 = 1.8e3, so 3",
        "credit": "the better bibob"
    },
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #36": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "all time high in 2023 of bitcoin was 45000 USD, each dollar bill is 0.1mm = 1e-4m thickness. 45000*1e-4m = 4.5m, 0.",
        "credit": "the better bibob"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #53": {
        "question": "Express Coulomb\u2019s constant 8.99 \u00d7 10^9 kg m^3 /s^2 C^2 using the units (picogram)(smoot)^2 (miles)/ (Planck time)(femtosecond)(exacoulomb)(yottacoulomb)",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "the coulombs constant listed just isnt the constant lol",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #91 [2019 Cheyenne Mountain Q44]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "There were 100 million Mongols at its height. This means that assuming a mongol can hoard 50 boards in their lifetime(a low estimate) 8+2 = 10.",
        "credit": "X"
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #13": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "489 gallons/year per car. 1.5e9 cars in world. Multiply to get 7.5e11 --> 12 is answer.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (rafaelnadal) 17-18, #7": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "world record bench press is 635 kg -> 635,000 g -> 635,000 mL water. shouldn\u2019t that round up to 10^6 because it is greater than 500,000",
        "credit": "quercus alba"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "27",
        "explanation": "energy released is 2.5 kJ/mol butane, so 6e23 * 2.5e3 = 27",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #1": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "17",
        "explanation": "Actual distance to Sirius is 8.15*10^16 meters, so it should be 17.\n \n8.6 light years * 9.44 * 10^15 meters per light year reaches the same conclusion, so 17 is correct, not 16.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #35": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-3",
        "explanation": "The probability of two people having the same birthday is 1/365 which should be -3 but the answer provided is -2",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 23-24, #6": {
        "question": "How many gallons of ice cream are consumed in the United States each year?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "GullSO Invitational 23-24, #35": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "20",
        "explanation": "Wolfram Alpha. (Alternatively, 100log(phi) - 1/2log(5) = 20.89-0.35 = 20.52, which is a comfortable 20.)",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #14 [2019 Captains Tryout: Seven Lakes Q6]": {
        "question": "What is the half-life of Carbon-14 in seconds?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Question originally didn't give units",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #32": {
        "question": "If every insect alive at this time played \u201cFlight of the Bumblebee\u201d on a tiny tuba, on repeat, how many notes could they play in a day?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Otherwise the answer is implying it is played once, not constantly over 24 hours.",
        "credit": "X"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "If we assume all of Steph\u2019s 3 pointers have come from the 3 point line how many times could we travel from the Earth to the Sun with the total distance the ball has traveled in these shots?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Unclear wording",
        "credit": "X"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 18-19, #9": {
        "question": "How many pet rabbits are there in the United States [#]?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Changing misspelling",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #61 [2019 Captains Tryout: TJHSST Q25]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "distance from LA to NY is 2000 miles, 25mpg means 80 gallons, 33kwh in each gallon and 3.6e6 joules in each kwh. 80*33*3.6e6 = about 9e9 joules. 4e3 joules in a kilocalorie so 9e9/4e3 = 2.25e6, so 6",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #17": {
        "question": "What is the product of the past six math problems (11 - 16)? [UNSOLVABLE QUESTION]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Remove this question because there is no way to solve it.",
        "credit": "X"
    },
    "Raisbeck Aviation Invitational 17-18, #30": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-19",
        "explanation": "The \"corrected\" explanation seems to think a nanometer is 0.001 m (a millimeter) and is incorrect. The original answer is correct.",
        "credit": "cubicfrog on discord"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #27": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "37",
        "explanation": "The world population is about 8 billion, the average human mass is 62 kg = 6.2e4 g, 1g = 6.022e23 dalton, so the combined mass is 8e9 x 6.2e4 g x 6.022e23 dalton/g = 2.98 x 10^37 dalton, so the answer is 37",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "University of Georgia Invitational 18-19, #18": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "Football field is 160\u00d7360 ft., 57,600 sq ft or 5,350 sq meters. Baseball diameter is just under 3 inches, therefore you could fit at least 16 in a square foot. Previous answer of 4 assumes that you are fitting one tennis ball per square meter, which makes no sense.",
        "credit": "yert"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #25 [2018 Captains Exchange: Roslyn Q16]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "21",
        "explanation": "bruh just google it how are people this incompetent",
        "credit": "rama BULUSU"
    },
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #23": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "24",
        "explanation": "Volume of the moon is 2e10 km3 - this should already suggest how wrong the answer is. This is 2e25 cm3, and using an estimate of a hersheys kiss volume being 10ish cm3 (although it hardly matters) it takes 10^24 kisses to make the moon by volume. If you do it by mass, the moon weighs 7e22 kg or 7e25 g, each kiss weighing according to the internet abt 5 g, in which case the answer should be 25. literally no idea how the answer could possibly be 10.",
        "credit": "disc: cubicfrog"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #42": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "Usain Bolt's top speed (about 27.8 mph or 44.7 km/h).\nThe length of the equator (about 40,075 kilometers).\nIf we divide the length of the equator by Usain Bolt's top speed, we can estimate the number of hours it would take him to run it. Then, we can convert hours to days.\n\n40,075 km / 44.7 km/h = 896.75 hours\n\nSo, it would take Usain Bolt approximately 897 hours to run along the equator. To convert this to days, we divide by 24 hours per day:\n\n897 hours / 24 hours/day \u2248 37.38 days\n\nSo, it would take Usain Bolt around 37 days to run along the equator if he maintained his top speed.",
        "credit": "quercus alba"
    },
    "GullSO Invitational 23-24, #31": {
        "question": "The 1936 Berlin Olympics Stadium was later used as a bunker by Nazis during WWII. How many people could it hold?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UMass Amherst Invitational 22-23, #37": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "52 choose 5 idk how people suck this much ass at mathematics",
        "credit": "rama"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #33 [2019 Carmel Q20]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "google it ur tweaking",
        "credit": "ryan park"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #77 [2019 CMU Q29]": {
        "question": "If the sun was replaced with the equivalent volume of maple syrup, what would its mass be in grams?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #41 [2018 Carmel Tryouts Q29]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "14",
        "explanation": "Thickness of quarter is about 1mm = 1e-3 m (previous person who corrected this said 1 mm = 1e-4 m), Earth-Sun distance is 1.5e11 m, so total quarters needed is 1.5e11 / 1e-3 = 1.5e14, so the answer is 14",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #10": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "26 = 2.6e1. Theres probably a typo but idk the original quesiton",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #5": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "https://journals.ametsoc.org/view/journals/clim/18/6/jcli-3299.1.xml\n5.1 x 10^18 kg is the figure given by this paper",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #26": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "23",
        "explanation": "the oceans are e24mL, and a gulp is about e1mL, giving e23 gulps",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #20": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "18",
        "explanation": "just google",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #27": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-6",
        "explanation": "earth to moon is 400000km --> 4e7m, each cell has 1.8 meters and 37 trillion cells --> 7e13m of dna. 4e7/7e13 = 6e-7 --> -6",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #125 [2018 Medford Q17]": {
        "question": "How many light-years across is the visible universe?",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "Question text is kinda flawed (original text \"How many light-years is the visible universe?\" leaves the ambiguity of radius or total length/diameter; total length is likely implied) but the observable universe (including the particle horizon) is ~46.5 billion light years in radius. This means the diameter is 93 billion light years, so the answer is 11. If the question were talking about radius we would round down to 10.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Brown Invitational 22-23, #7": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "3",
        "explanation": "the person who corrected it initially claimed that they have 541 wins. assuming this is correct, the answer rounds up to 3 not 2. the original answer is correct.",
        "credit": "yert"
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #40": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "21",
        "explanation": "1.3 * 10^21 L of water in oceans, each balloon is 0.35 L, so ans is gonna be 21",
        "credit": "teenmoturtle"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #46 [2018 Columbia Q11]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "51.8 million american travellers in 2017, so ans should be 8",
        "credit": "teenmoturtle"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #13": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "modern cpu examples: amd ryzen 9, intel i9, both have close to 10 billion transistors, so ans should be 10",
        "credit": "teenmoturtle"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "There are 26,000 high schools in indonesia as of 2024 and 2023",
        "credit": "TanMan"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #29": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "look it up",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #43 [2018 Pembroke Q25]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "E. Coli is 2 micrometers, Upstate New York has a width of about 500 km, so 5*10^5 m/2 * 10^-6 m =2.5 * 10^11, which is 11 (idk how they got 15?????)",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #18": {
        "question": "What is the radius of the moon? [m]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #14": {
        "question": "How many students could be put through elementary and secondary school with the amount of money found in the question above? [Military budget of the US]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "arisu"
    },
    "Palo Alto Tryouts 22-23, #35": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "According to google there are 70,000 public elementary schools in the us and 18,000 private elementary schools which adds up to around 100,000 AKA 10^5.",
        "credit": "TopekaKansas"
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #5": {
        "question": "What is the surface area of North America? (square kilometers)",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "google",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #52": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "90",
        "explanation": "Simplifying R value units gives that [R] = K m^2 / W = K s^3 kg^-1. In Planck units, R value is the Planck temperature times the Planck time cubed divided by the Planck mass, which gives (1.42e32*(5.39*10^-44)^3)/(2.18*10^-8)=1.02e-90. This means that there are 10^90 Planck R in an SI R, so the answer should be +90.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "How many M&Ms would fit within the sun?",
        "answer": "33",
        "explanation": "There are approximately 10^3 M&M's per liter (using online sources), and 10^3 liters in a meter cubed. The sun's volume can be calculated to be 4 x 10^18 Km3 (using r=10^6 Km). There are 10^9 m3 in a km3 so the final equation is 10^3 x 10^3 x 10^9 x 4 x 10^18, or ~ 10^33 M&M's in the sun.",
        "credit": "JazzyX"
    },
    "GullSO Invitational 23-24, #36": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "theres not even 10^20 numbers from 0 to 1 million. the frequency of happy numbers is about 0.1 so 5",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "For some reason, the very specific Google search for \"surface area of a blue whale\" didn't give me anything (except maybe being put on an EPA watch list), but the length is known to be about 24 meters on average, and the width is known to be about 4 meters. If we approximate the body of a blue whale as a cylinder (it could be worse), we get about 300 m^2 for the surface area. For toothpicks, we know their dimensions are 64 mm in length and 2 mm in thickness, the total amount of toothpicks that fit on the blue whale is 300 m^2 / (0.064*0.002 m^2) \u2248 2.5 * 10^6, so the answer is 6.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #41": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "PVA molar mass is 86.09",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #17": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Earth's surface area is approximately 5* 10^14, and 30% of that is land, so there is about 1.5 *10^14 sq meters of land on the Earth. Divide that by population of roughly 8 billion = 1.87*10^4 sq. m /person",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #17": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "1kgU*(4*10^6MJ/1kgU)=4*10^6MJ=4*10^12J=10^9Kcal*(1mi/100Kcal)=10^7mi->7",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #121 [2019 Captains Tryout: Seven Lakes Q24]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "Wellington to London is 18776km, Suez Canal is 193km, 18776/193=97 -> 2",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #47 [2018 Polytechnic Q2]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "10-12% of people are left handed. There are 8 billion people in the world. That is roughy 800,000,000 - 960,000,000 which is 10^8",
        "credit": "Evan&Matt"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #8": {
        "question": "You\u2019re halfway through the test and you think \u201cThis test is so dumb. Where are the questions that are like \u2018What\u2019s 7 raised to the 34th power?\u2019\u201d What\u2019s 7^(-34)",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 23-24, #49": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "im pretty sure thats more than 1 question lol",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #11": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "ssn is 9 digits, highest one starts with a 5 so like, isnt it 10 then",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #8": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-5",
        "explanation": "the ratio is 1:1.7 for miles to kilometers, not 1:1600.",
        "credit": "Mang223"
    },
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #5": {
        "question": "What is the probability that everyone in a family of 4 survives the virus? [Virus that escaped containment, kills 90% of population]",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #29": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "The density is not 19.3 x 10^-4 g/m^3, that\u2019s way too light. The actual density is 19.3 x 10^6 g/m^3 and since the volume of the empire state building is 1,000,000 m^3, the mass would be around 20 x 10^12 or 13 as the answer",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #6": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "17",
        "explanation": "surface area of jupiter divide by (SA of a playing card *54) gives 17",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "divide the perimeter of the United States by 2000 gives 25940.5 watchtowers. -> 4",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #4": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "58",
        "explanation": "question gives answer in kilocalories technically, so mult by 1000 so 58",
        "credit": "teenmoturtle"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #19": {
        "question": "5^222",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "None"
    },
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #9": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "23",
        "explanation": "11 cubic cm = 11ml = 11g = 11/18.02 ~ 0.5 mol = ~3e23 molecules",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Harvard Invitational 22-23, #6": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "~",
        "explanation": "answer is negative???",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #30": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "20",
        "explanation": "15 A = 15 coulombs/second. Divide 15 coulombs by the charge of an electron (1.6*10^-19) to get 9.38^19 --> 20",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #35": {
        "question": "How many letters are utilized by this very quirky sentence?",
        "answer": "1",
        "explanation": "The \"History ...\" part was the beginning of the next section after that; regardless, every sentence in the question has less than 50 characters",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #41": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Can this question be removed or details added to make it answerable",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #46": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "26",
        "explanation": "The volume of the Atlantic Ocean is about 3.5e8 km^3 = 3.5e17 m^3, which multiplied by the density of water (1e3 kg/m^3) becomes 3.5e20 kg = 3.5e23 g. The specific heat of water is 4.184 J/(g K) and we probably need to heat up all the water by an average of 90 K (because the average temperature of ocean water is around 10 C\u00b0 (accounting for the very cold water below the surface), the energy needed for the water to get to boiling point is 3.5e23 g * 4.184 J/(g K) * 90 K = 1.3e27 J = 3.2e25 cal. BUT WAIT, we need to account for the latent heat of evaporation, which is 2260 J/g = 540 cal/g, so our final answer is 3.2e25 cal + 3.5e23 g * 540 cal/g = 2.2e26 cal, so the answer is 26.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Harvard Invitational 22-23, #7": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "25",
        "explanation": "Speed of light c = (3e8 m/s) * (1 carbon radius / 1.7e-10 m) * (3.2e7 s / 1 year) * (1 year / 5 dog years) = 1.1e25 carbon radii/dog year. It turns out that dog years apparently don't scale linearly with time until a certain age (why?????), but after that it scales to about 5 dog years per year.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #35": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "It's 7^16 dumbass",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Rickards Invitational 23-24, #46": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "Average adult male has 36 trillion cells, average adult female has 28 trillion cells, difference is 8 trillion cells which is 13.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #80 [2018 Medford Q11]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "Earth-Sun distance is 1.5e11 m, length of popsicle stick (accounting for glue) is about 3.5-4 inches = ~0.095 m, so the number of sticks needed is 1.5e11 / 0.095 = 1.6e12, so the answer is 12.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #6": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "15",
        "explanation": "4.367 ly = 4.13e16 m, using speed of 100 m / 9.58 s = 10.44 m/s, total time is 4.13e16 m /10.44 m/s = 3.96e15 s, so the answer is 15",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Ohio State Invitational 22-23, #26": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "tangential speed of earth is ~ 1000 mph\n1000 * 24 * 7 = 168000\n5",
        "credit": "teenmoturtle"
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "41",
        "explanation": "volume of milky way = 3 * 10^61\nvolume of earth = 10^20\n61 - 20 = 41",
        "credit": "teenmoturtle"
    },
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #52": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "65536 is the result",
        "credit": "cindyxxmel"
    },
    "University of Michigan Invitational 18-19, #20": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-9",
        "explanation": "SEMs have resolutions of 0.5-4 nanometers. That corresponds with -9",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 23-24, #40": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "Real earth radius = 6 million meters, real Jupiter radius = 70 million meters. Soccer ball has a radius of 11 cm, so scaled down Jupiter would have a radius of 70/6 * 0.11 = 1.28m, and a volume of 4/3*pi*(1.28)^3 = 8.8m^3 = 8800 L \u2014> 4",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #4": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "13",
        "explanation": "30 trillion --> 13 according to https://www.healthline.com/health/number-of-cells-in-body",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "FermiSweat, Fermi Questions, but butter (chicken), #17": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "According to this source (might be wrong), https://rentechdigital.com/smartscraper/business-report-details/india/restaurants, there are 250k restaurants in India, meaning we would have to visit 125k --> 5, in order to have a 50% chance of finding the correct one. Other sources site 500k - 1M restaurants but I have not seen anything above 1M so the answer should still be 5",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #93 [2018 Iolani Q17]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-9",
        "explanation": "google",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #6 [2019 WWPS Q4]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "53",
        "explanation": "(3.8e26 W) * (3.2e7 s) / (1e-19 J) = ~1.2e53",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #18": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "19",
        "explanation": "4.17*10^12 m^3 -> 4.17*10^18 cm^3, an m&m takes up about 0.65 cm of space so 4.17/0.65 * 10^18 which is clearly 19.",
        "credit": "bibob"
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #24": {
        "question": "Muons have a half life of 1.56*10^-6 seconds. I stand at rest and observe a million muon particles travel from one end of a 10^4 meter tunnel to another end, at velocity v=0.8c, where c is the speed of light. How many muons reach the end?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #20": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "Baseball volume is ~2e-1 L, Olympic swimming pool is 2.5e6 L, so number is 2.5e6 / 2e-1 which is about 1e7, so the answer is 7.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 23-24, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "1998",
        "explanation": "Since the power of n is 999, we only really need the last term to approximate the series, so the sum is 100^999 = 10^1998, meaning the answer is 1998. Note that the ratio of the 99th term to the 100th term is (99/100)^999 = 4.36e-5, so only the 100th term is actually important.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #8": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "Metric ton is 1e6 g, each bill has a mass of about 1 g (according to the US government), so 1e6 * $100 * 100 c/$ = 1e10 cents, so the answer is 10",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "0",
        "explanation": "A male cries 1.3 times on average per month. 1/10 of a gram in a liter of coke. 30 days in a month. This is just 0.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #32": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "Mass of neptune is 10^26, while the mass of earth is 6x10^24. this ratio is 2.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #83 [2019 Centerville Q13]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "22",
        "explanation": "10^21 liters in the earths ocean, 1/20 liters per balloon. 22",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "MIT Invitational 21-22, #45": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "The US uses 4000 TWh/year=1.4*10^19J/year. Wood has an energy density of 7*10^6J/lb. 1.4*10^19J/year * 1lb/(7*10^6J)=2*10^12lb/year -> 12",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #48": {
        "question": "Based on the previous question, if you randomly placed a guess between -98 and 98 for every question, what is the probability that you receive either partial or full credit on every question?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Please provide an explanation of the \"previous question\"",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #23": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "its been some time so now its at 195m views with approx 1.5 years ago, thats like 195/450 which is less than 0.5 so now its rounding down. L taylor",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #15": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "Sun diameter (1.4 million km) / 6 inches (phone length) = ~9e9 --> 10",
        "credit": "eddyzow"
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #34": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "1 cumulonimbus cloud is 1 million tonnes = 1 billion kg = 1billion liters -> 9",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #43": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "A typical cloud weighs 1 million pounds - some google sources talk about ones weighing much larger, these are the rarest of massive clouds that we can see.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #38": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "42",
        "explanation": "If mogwai reproduce at 5 per 10 seconds, then there are 60 periods of reproduction in a 10-minute period, and so the answer is 5^60",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #37": {
        "question": "What is the ratio between the amount of storage taken up by Red Dead Redemption 2 and Brawl Stars?",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "150GB for RDR2, 350MB for Brawl. 150,000/350=400 -> 2",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 23-24, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "111 million entries according to wikipedia (my history teacher won't be happy about Wikipedia)",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "Did you know that french fries are actually from Belgium? Hopefully! How many servings of deep-fried french fries would it take to equal the yearly caloric intake of an elephant?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdBird"
    },
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 23-24, #10": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "Soccer field is 105 m x 68 m = 7.14e3 m^2, Mars surface area is 4 pi * (3.4e6 m)^2 = 1.45e14 m^2. Dividing, we get 2.0e10, so the answer is 10.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 23-24, #5": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "I checked several sources online and they all seem to agree that the average American spends a little less than $1000 on Christmas. Multiplying that by the population of the US gives an upper bound of 3.5e11 dollars. Of course not everyone in the US contributes to the number (young children are probably excluded) but the resulting answer would be lower than the upper bound and still round to 10^11. Therefore, the answer is 11.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Rickards Invitational 23-24, #27": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "41",
        "explanation": "One barn is 100 square femtometers, or 10^-28 m^2. The Roman Empire was apparently 5.0e6 km^2 = 5.0e12 m^2 at its peak in the 2nd century CE under Trajan. This problem is hilariously unlucky since if we divide 5.0e12 by 1e-28, we get 5.0e40 which rounds up to 41.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #45": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "5",
        "explanation": "average pencil draws a line 2-3 km long, earth's circumference is 2pi * 6378km = 40074km long, 16000 pencils needed, pencil is 7.5in long on average, so 4 + 1 = 5 inches of pencil required",
        "credit": "choi"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 23-24, #34": {
        "question": "How many digits does 13^123456789 have?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "randomeclipse"
    },
    "SOUP Invitational 23-24, #37": {
        "question": "If the sun and earth both double in size, how long in seconds will it take for the earth to go around the sun?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ".waful (discord)"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #40": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "2",
        "explanation": "The wavelength of violet light is 380 nm",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #100 [2018 Kenston Q28]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "US-Mexico border length is around 3000 km = 3e6 m (google), total volume is therefore 3e6m * 2m * thickness. The question was kind of vague about the thickness but given the context of this problem a rather thick wall of around 0.5 m (or more) is likely implied. As a result (using thickness 0.5 m), the wall has a total volume of 3.6e6 m^3, and since brick density is on average about 1.8e3 kg/m^3, the total mass of the wall is 5.4e9 kg, which rounds up to 10.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #39 [2019 NCS Q4]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-6",
        "explanation": "Two solve paths: 1 million earths fit in sun, so 1/10^6->-6, or radius of sun = 7*10^5km, radius of earth = 6500km, ((7*10^3)/(7*10^5))^3=10^-6->-6",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #112 [2019 Boyceville Q23]": {
        "question": "What is the density of a neutron star in kg/m^3?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": "BirdyBirdyBirdyBird"
    },
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #43": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "20",
        "explanation": "Volume of Pacific Ocean is 7.14e8 km^3 = 7.14e17 m^3 = 7.14e20 L, bowling ball volume is around 5000 cm^3 = 5 L, so our final answer is 7.13e20 / 5e0 = 1.4e20, so the final answer is 20.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #106 [2019 NCS Q1]": {
        "question": "How many minutes are there in a century?",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "3.1e7 seconds in a year roughly translates to a little more than 5e5 minutes in a year so 6 + 2 = 8",
        "credit": "ac"
    },
    "University of Georgia Invitational 18-19, #4": {
        "question": "If you earned a penny for every 10 steps you walk, how much cents will you earn by the time you are 40 years old?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #13": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "duke chapel is 64 m tall, which is 6*10^7 micrometers --> 8",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #6": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "6",
        "explanation": "The surface area of the pyramid of Giza measures approximately 10^5 m^2 and the surface area of a sticky note measures approximately 10^-1 m^2, therefore the answer is 10^5/10^-1 = 10^6 m^2.",
        "credit": "Kian and Leo"
    },
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #52": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "Global energy consumption is about 6* 10^21 joules. one hair dryer is around 1000 W, so over the course of the year it would consume 3* 10^10 Joules (3* 10^7 seconds * 1000 W). In order to be equivalent to double the yearly consumption, the energy the hair dryers consume needs to be to the power of 22, so 10^12 hair dryers are needed. --> 12",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #16": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "Depends which way the snickers bars are stacked, horizontally or vertically",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 22-23, #18": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "Most sources online actually say 7.5*10^18 grains of sand, not ^21. Using the same number of stars in the milky way gives an answer of 19-11 = 8.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 23-24, #21": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "9",
        "explanation": "I found a few estimates online for food waste per student and it seems that around 25-50% of food is wasted by students (so like a quarter to a half of every meal). I will round to 50% to account for additional food that is produced but never served (yeah this problem is depressing). There are around 53 million K-12 students in the US, which are mostly served lunch by the school they attend (some get breakfast too and some bring their own food but it should balance out more or less), so about 20 days per month. Therefore, the number of meals wasted (i.e. the number of meals that could be produced with the waste) is 0.5 x 5.3e7 x 20 = 5.3e8 which rounds up to 9 (kind of on the fence about this one but the original answer of 6 is definitely wrong).",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #26": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "15",
        "explanation": "surface area is 5 * 10^14 meters. \u2014> 15",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "UT Austin Invitational 23-24, #44": {
        "question": "What is auto?",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #3": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-4",
        "explanation": "Toothpick diameter is ~1.5 mm = 1.5e-3 m, green light wavelength is around 550 nm = 5.5e-7 m. Dividing these numbers gives 3.67e-4, so the answer is -4.",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #48 [2018 Centerville Q4]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "7",
        "explanation": "Mt. Everest height/width of penny = 8.849*10^3/(1.5*10^-3) = 5.8*10^6 = 7",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #24": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "10",
        "explanation": "the US imports 8.33 million barrels of oil/day (https://www.eia.gov/energyexplained/oil-and-petroleum-products/imports-and-exports.php) times 365 days = 3* 10^10 barrels a year.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Case Western Reserve University 23-24, #14": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-10",
        "explanation": "Bohr radius is 5.2e-11 m, so the answer is -10",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "UMass Amherst Invitational 22-23, #31": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "14",
        "explanation": "Using the relativistic kinetic energy formula: KE = mc^2 * (1/sqrt(1-(v/c)^2) - 1), and substituting v/c = 0.01 and m = 60-80 kg gives an answer range of 2.700-3.600e14 J. Note that since v/c \u2248 0, the non-relativistic kinetic energy formula also gives 2.7-3.6e14 J, so the answer is 14",
        "credit": "errorfunction"
    },
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #28": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "22",
        "explanation": "1 mol of any gas at standard conditions is 22.4 liters. A lays bag is probably 1 liter or so at max of oxygen, so 6e23/20 is about 3e22->22.",
        "credit": "emptiespace"
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #99 [2018 Fairfax Q5b]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "15",
        "explanation": "distance from South Africa to Australia = 10^4km = 10^7 m = 10^15 angstroms",
        "credit": "chyler"
    },
    "Princeton Invitational 23-24, #40": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "15",
        "explanation": "look it up dumbass",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 23-24, #22": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "12",
        "explanation": "Sun explodes in 7 billion years, times 150 goals / year = about 1 trillion years --> 12",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 23-24, #30": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "11",
        "explanation": "Rain per thunderstorm is 2e6 kg, mass of raindrop is ~3e-5 kg. by DIVISION we get 11 as answer",
        "credit": "shut ur bitchass up"
    },
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 23-24, #10": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "8",
        "explanation": "On average, the Postal Service processes and delivers 162.1 million pieces of First-Class Mail each day. On average, the Postal Service processes 318 million mail pieces each day, 13.3 million each hour, 221,080 each minute and 3,684 each second.\n\nfrom google <3",
        "credit": "Rama BULUSU"
    },
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #27": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "4",
        "explanation": "The length of the Golden Gate Bridge is 8,981 ft. The width of a CD is 4.7 in, or 0.39 ft. 8981/0.39 = 22930 CDs -> 4.",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #23": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-13",
        "explanation": "Human cell contains about 6 * 10^-12 grams or 6 * 10^-15 kg; thus weighs ~6 * 10^-14",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #109 [2019 Athens Q18]": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "",
        "explanation": "football field is 120 yd by 50 yd and baseball is 3.7 cm radius, do math",
        "credit": ""
    },
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #10": {
        "question": "",
        "answer": "-8",
        "explanation": "moon mass 7e22 kg and sun mass 2e30 kg, MATHEMATICS gives 3.5e-8 roughly",
        "credit": ""
    }
}
corrections_list = [
    "UT Austin Invitational 18-19, #22",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #5",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "UT Austin Invitational 17-18, #19",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #25",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #6",
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #43",
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #13",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #6",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #18 [2018 Brown Q19]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #75 [2019 Polytechnic Q19]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #1",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #11 [2019 Eastside / Haslett Q14]",
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2019 LISO Q14]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #15",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #66 [2019 Northmont Q5]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #7",
    "Princeton Invitational 22-23, #33",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #22",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #34",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #16",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #26",
    "UT Austin Invitational 18-19, #13",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #1",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #16",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #16",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #18",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #16 [2018 Harvard Q4]",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #7",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #21",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #37",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #45",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #39",
    "UT Austin Invitational 22-23, #17",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #31",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #10",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #12",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #98 [2019 ATX Regionals Q41]",
    "University of Michigan Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #32",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2019 WWPN Q3]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #32",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #1",
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "SSSS Fermi (randomsci) 22-23, #23",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #3",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #21",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #40",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #67 [2018 WWPN Tryouts Q1]",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #10",
    "UT Austin Invitational 17-18, #21",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #85 [2018 U Georgia Q2]",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #16",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #131 [2019 New Trier Q10]",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #5",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #14",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #3",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #36",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #60",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #27",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #6",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #1",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #33 [2018 Westlake Q47]",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #31",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #33",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #10",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #31",
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #7",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #110 [2019 Monta Vista Q22]",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #12",
    "SSSS Fermi (randomsci) 22-23, #27",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #38",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #49",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #22",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #19",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #1",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #11",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #7",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #41",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #6 [2019 Virginia Tech Q4]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #22 [2018 Acton-Box Q15]",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #46",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #1",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #80 [2019 U Chicago Q21]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #109 [2018 U Florida Regionals Q14]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #96 [2018 Monta Vista Tryouts Q1]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #41",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "SSSS Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #20",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #17 [2018 Westlake Q24]",
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #30",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #27",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #41",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #133 [2019 Dartmouth Q16]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #73 [2019 Northmont Q75]",
    "SSSs Fermi (rafaelnadal) 17-18, #34",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #111 [2019 SOUP Q38]",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #41",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #2",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #18",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2018 Princeton Q A39]",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #21",
    "MIT Invitational 21-22, #36",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #21",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #2",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #12",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #18",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #36",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #21",
    "Rickards SO Invitational 22-23, #42",
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #17",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #2",
    "Harvard Invitational 22-23, #4",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #53 [2018 Westlake Q27]",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #38",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #24",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #41",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #2",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #5",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #3 [2018 Princeton Q B9]",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #13",
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #42",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #43",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #125 [2018 Centerville Q18]",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #39",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #34 [2019 Captains Exchange: NCSSM Q15]",
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #3",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #35 [2019 Solon Q9]",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #47",
    "Ohio State Invitational 22-23, #8",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #37",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #82 [2019 Captains Exchange: Irvine Q10]",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #19",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #26 [2018 Aviation Q5]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #105 [2019 Polytechnic Q24]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #60 [2019 Boca Raton Tryouts Q11]",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #2",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #25",
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #47",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #21",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #36 [2019 Boca Raton Tryouts Q29]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #53 [2018 Westlake Q27]",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #3",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #13",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #5",
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #20",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #14",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #12",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #13",
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #17",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #39",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #116 [2019 Columbia Q3]",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #8",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #14",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #10",
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #38",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #120 [2018 Westlake Q44]",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #3",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #1 [2018 Westlake Q64]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #19",
    "UT Austin Invitational 23-24, #9",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #114 [2019 Solon Q10]",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #53",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #49",
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #26",
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2019 Duke Q5]",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #4",
    "Rickards Invitational 23-24, #45",
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #44",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #2",
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #22",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #14",
    "Palo Alto Tryouts 22-23, #31",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "Princeton Invitational 22-23, #12",
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #40",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #77 [2019 Cornell Q28]",
    "UMass Amherst Invitational 22-23, #34",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #12",
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #2",
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #25",
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #30",
    "SOAPS Invitational 22-23, #25",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #12",
    "Clements Invitational 17-18, #2",
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #34",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #96 [2018 Monta Vista Tryouts Q15]",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #46",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #4",
    "Ohio State Invitational 22-23, #8",
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #17",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #35 [2018 SOUP Q25]",
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #21",
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #8",
    "Ohio State Invitational 22-23, #8",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #50",
    "BirdSO Invitational 20-21, #40",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #15 [2018 Mesa-Wilson Q43]",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #9",
    "Princeton Invitational 17-18, #47",
    "Rice Invitational 17-18, #10",
    "MIT Invitational 17-18, #34",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #44 [2018 SOUP Q4]",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #14",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #44",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #36",
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #53",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #91 [2019 Cheyenne Mountain Q44]",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #13",
    "SSSs Fermi (rafaelnadal) 17-18, #7",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #24",
    "University of Georgia Invitational 23-24, #17",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #1",
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #35",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #34 [2019 Captains Exchange: NCSSM Q15]",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 23-24, #6",
    "GullSO Invitational 23-24, #35",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #14 [2019 Captains Tryout: Seven Lakes Q6]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #32",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #15",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "Princeton Invitational 18-19, #9",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #61 [2019 Captains Tryout: TJHSST Q25]",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #17",
    "Raisbeck Aviation Invitational 17-18, #30",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #27",
    "University of Georgia Invitational 18-19, #18",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #25 [2018 Captains Exchange: Roslyn Q16]",
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #23",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #42",
    "GullSO Invitational 23-24, #31",
    "UMass Amherst Invitational 22-23, #37",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #33 [2018 Westlake Q47]",
    "Rickards SO Invitational 22-23, #42",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #33 [2019 Carmel Q20]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #77 [2019 CMU Q29]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #11",
    "Raisbeck Aviation Invitational 17-18, #30",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #41 [2018 Carmel Tryouts Q29]",
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #10",
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #5",
    "Camas Invitational 22-23, #26",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #20",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #27",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #125 [2018 Medford Q17]",
    "Brown Invitational 22-23, #7",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #40",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #46 [2018 Columbia Q11]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #13",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 22-23, #24",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #29",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #85 [2018 U Georgia Q2]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #43 [2018 Pembroke Q25]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #102 [2019 Duke Q5]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #18",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 22-23, #18",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #14",
    "Palo Alto Tryouts 22-23, #35",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #5",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 18-19, #26",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #125 [2018 Medford Q17]",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #21",
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #52",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #14",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "Raisbeck Aviation Invitational 17-18, #30",
    "GullSO Invitational 23-24, #36",
    "Carolina Invitational 22-23, #31",
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #3",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #41",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #17",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #17",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #21",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #121 [2019 Captains Tryout: Seven Lakes Q24]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #47 [2018 Polytechnic Q2]",
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #8",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 23-24, #49",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #11",
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #8",
    "UT Austin Regionals 22-23, #5",
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #8",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #29",
    "University of Michigan Invitational 17-18, #6",
    "MIT Invitational 17-18, #34",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #22",
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #4",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #19",
    "Cornell Invitational 22-23, #9",
    "Harvard Invitational 22-23, #6",
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #30",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #77 [2019 CMU Q29]",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #35",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #41",
    "Brown Invitational 22-23, #7",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #46",
    "Harvard Invitational 22-23, #7",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #35",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #49",
    "Rickards Invitational 23-24, #46",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #80 [2018 Medford Q11]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #41 [2018 Carmel Tryouts Q29]",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #6",
    "Ohio State Invitational 22-23, #26",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #14",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #52",
    "Brown Invitational 22-23, #7",
    "University of Michigan Invitational 18-19, #20",
    "Brown Invitational 22-23, #7",
    "SOUP Invitational 23-24, #40",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 22-23, #4",
    "FermiSweat, Fermi Questions, but butter (chicken), #17",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #93 [2018 Iolani Q17]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #6 [2019 WWPS Q4]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #18",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #24",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #105 [2019 Polytechnic Q24]",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #24",
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #47",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #20",
    "UT Austin Invitational 23-24, #21",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #8",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #35 [2019 Solon Q9]",
    "Centerville Invitational 17-18, #8",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #24",
    "MIT Invitational 18-19, #21",
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #32",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #83 [2019 Centerville Q13]",
    "MIT Invitational 21-22, #45",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #48",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #23",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #14",
    "SSSs Fermi (luminosityfan) 17-18, #15",
    "Captains Tryouts Carmel 17-18, #5",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #16",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #34",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #43",
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #38",
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #37",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #77 [2019 CMU Q29]",
    "SOUP Invitational 23-24, #22",
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #31",
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 23-24, #10",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 23-24, #5",
    "Rickards Invitational 23-24, #27",
    "Columbia Invitational 17-18, #45",
    "SOUP Invitational 23-24, #34",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #66 [2019 Northmont Q5]",
    "SOUP Invitational 23-24, #37",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #40",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #100 [2018 Kenston Q28]",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #39 [2019 NCS Q4]",
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #8",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #112 [2019 Boyceville Q23]",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #43",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #106 [2019 NCS Q1]",
    "University of Georgia Invitational 18-19, #4",
    "Duke Invitational 22-23, #13",
    "Sahil Gandhi, WSO Regionals 22-23, #6",
    "Golden Gate Invitational 22-23, #52",
    "UChicago Invitational 22-23, #16",
    "UT Austin Invitational 22-23, #18",
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 23-24, #21",
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #26",
    "UT Austin Invitational 23-24, #44",
    "BullSO Invitational 22-23, #3",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #48 [2018 Centerville Q4]",
    "SOUP Invitational 22-23, #50",
    "SSSS Fermi (Adi1008) 17-18, #24",
    "BirdSO Satellite Invitational 21-22, #35",
    "Case Western Reserve University 23-24, #14",
    "UMass Amherst Invitational 22-23, #31",
    "North Pocono Invitational 22-23, #28",
    "High Desert Satellite Invitational 23-24, #40",
    "UT Austin Invitational 22-23, #18",
    "BirdSO In-Person Invitational 22-23, #5",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #99 [2018 Fairfax Q5b]",
    "Princeton Invitational 23-24, #40",
    "BirdSO Mini Invitational 21-22, #22",
    "Carnegie Mellon Invitational 22-23, #5",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #29",
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 23-24, #22",
    "Highlands Virtual Invitational 23-24, #30",
    "High Desert Mini Invitational 23-24, #10",
    "University of Florida North Regional 17-18, #27",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #106 [2019 NCS Q1]",
    "Seven Lakes Invitational 17-18, #23",
    "RobertYL, daily fermi questions day #109 [2019 Athens Q18]",
    "Yale Invitational 17-18, #10",
    "MIT Invitational 22-23, #35",
    "Northview Invitational 23-24, #26"
]